<resources>
    <string name="app_name">BenefitProgram</string>
    <string name="hello_world">Hello world!</string>
    <string name="action_info">Information</string>
    <string name="title_activity_child_disability">ChildDisability</string>
    <string name="title_activity_gsthst">GSTHST</string>
    <string name="title_activity_ncbs">NCBS</string>
    <string name="title_activity_cctb">CCTB</string>
    <string name="crawebsite"><a href="http://www.cra-arc.gc.ca/menu-eng.html">Canada Revenue Agency</a></string>
    <string name="title_activity_cctbinfo">CCTBInfo</string>
    <string name="cctb_info">
        CCTB/NCBS Guideline Table effective July 2014 -June 2015.
        Notes:
        1 Slight variances exist for the basic benefit amount for residents of Alberta.
    2 These amounts are for the Federal CCTB program (basic benefit plus National Child Benefit Supplement)
    exclusive of any amount to which a recipient may be eligible under any existing provincial or territorial benefit or credit program.
    3 These amounts are only to be used as a guideline. All recipients must keep Canada Revenue Agency informed of any changes
    to their family income, marital status, number of dependent children and current address.
    4 These amounts do not include the Child Disability Benefit (CDB).
    5,Universal Child Care Benefit (UCCB) or Registered Disability Savings Plan (RDSP) will not be included as part of your adjusted
     family net income in the calculation of your CCTB.
    </string>
    <string name="title_activity_childinfo">Childinfo</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="child_info">
        Child Disability Benefit Guideline Table effective July 2014 - June 2015
        ** The CDB base threshold is determined by the total number of children eligible for the CCTB as follows:
        Number of children,Base threshold
        1.$43,953
        2.$43,945
        3.$43,929
        4.$49,593
        5.$55,257
        6.$60,920
        7.$66,584
        8.$72,248
        The CDB base amount is calculated using the formula:
        F/H + $25,584 where:
        F is the annual entitlement of the NCBS amounts for each child.
       H equals the NCBS annual reduction rate for the total number of children
    </string>
    <string name="ncbsinfo" formatted="false">
    Monthly NCBS only entitlement - 2013 tax year (July 2014 - June 2015).
    Entitlement:
    $2,241 - 1st child
    $1,982 - 2nd child
    $1,886 - 3rd and each additional child
    Reduction rate:
    12.2% - 1 child
    23.0% - 2 children
    33.3% - 3 and more children
    Universal Child Care Benefit (UCCB) or Registered Disability Savings Plan (RDSP) will
    not be included as part of your adjusted family net income in the calculation of your CCTB.
    </string>
    <string name="title_activity_ncsbinfo">NCSBinfo</string>
    <string name="title_activity_gstinfo">GSTinfo</string>
    <string name="gst_info">
        GST-HST Credit : Guideline Table effective July 2014 - June 2015
        Notes:
        1.The amounts listed above represent a recipients yearly entitlement for the GST/HST credit
        based on their marital status, family size and family net income.
        2. The yearly entitlement for the 2013 tax year is paid in 4 quarterly issuances in the months of July and October 2014 and January and April 2015.
        3. These amounts are only to be used as a guideline
        4. All recipients must keep the Canada Revenue Agency informed of any changes to their current address, family size and marital situation.
        5. The Universal Child Care Benefit (UCCB) and/or Registered Disability Savings Plan (RDSP) are not to be included as part of your adjusted family net income in the calculation of your GST/HST credit.
    </string>

</resources>
